<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quasarplane Documentation – Container Service</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/container-service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Container Service on Quasarplane Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/container-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Container Service</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Quasarch&amp;rsquo;s Container Service is a decentralized, highly scalable, container management service that makes it easy to run and manage your containers on a serverless infrastructure.
This infrastructure is managed by Quasarch which launches your services and workloads on a Decentralized Compute Marketplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By using a decentralized protocol to lease resources from a global network of compute providers, we can offer our users a lower cost, censorship-resistant, localized hosting solution to run containers.
Container Service also supports a range of Nvidia GPUs to be used by containers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-decentralized&#34;&gt;Why decentralized?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks, also known as DePINs, are open and accessible networks, in contrast with traditional infrastructure that often end up with a centralized entity that dictates the terms and conditions for what users can do with the services provided.
This can have a direct negative impact on innovation, cost and user-experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Globally decentralized networks allow projects to be deployed on regions closer to where the business operates, bringing products closer to its users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quick-start&#34;&gt;Quick Start&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/&#34;&gt;Deploy your first container&lt;/a&gt; on the Decentralized Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Set up to use Container Service</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/setup/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;sign-up-for-a-quasarch-cloud-account&#34;&gt;Sign up for a Quasarch Cloud account&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do not have a Quasarch Cloud account, complete the following steps to create one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To sign up for a Quasarch Cloud account&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://console.quasarch.cloud/register&#34;&gt;https://console.quasarch.cloud/register&lt;/a&gt;.
Follow the online instructions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quasarch Cloud sends you a confirmation email after the sign-up process is complete.
At any time, you can view your current account activity and manage your account by going to &lt;a href=&#34;https://console.quasarch.cloud&#34;&gt;https://console.quasarch.cloud&lt;/a&gt; and clicking on your profile picture.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: User Guide for Container Service</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This user guide provides an introduction to decentralized containers and introductory step-by-step procedures to run them on Container Service.
Docker basics takes you through the basic steps to create a Docker container image and deploy it on Quasarch Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Deploying on Container Service</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/user-guide/deploy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page shows you how to deploy to Container Service a sample container that has already been pushed to a public registry (Docker Hub) in this case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;before-you-begin&#34;&gt;Before you Begin&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make sure you are logged into &lt;a href=&#34;https://console.quasarch.cloud/&#34;&gt;console&lt;/a&gt; and that you have enough credits to continue.
Be sure to delete all the resources you create after completing this guide so you avoid being charged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;creating-your-container&#34;&gt;Creating your Container&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To create a container deployment on Container Service, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From the navigation menu select the &lt;strong&gt;Compute&lt;/strong&gt; dropdown and then click on &lt;strong&gt;Container Service&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on &lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; to go to the form to create your container.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From here you&amp;rsquo;ll have to fill out the container creation form.
Make sure that you specify a public registry path as &lt;strong&gt;private registries are not yet supported&lt;/strong&gt;.
Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to include your image tag (when using the latest tag make sure to include &lt;code&gt;latest&lt;/code&gt; in the image).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;gpu-settings&#34;&gt;GPU Settings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Container Service supports running containers that leverage GPU support.
In case you select many different GPU models, your deployment will only run with access to one of those models.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-warning&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4 class=&#34;alert-heading&#34;&gt;Warning&lt;/h4&gt;

    GPUs can greatly increase the cost of running your container depending on the model.

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you are satisfied with the configuration click on &lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt;.
This action will redirect you to the container listing page where you&amp;rsquo;ll find your deployment as &lt;em&gt;deploying&lt;/em&gt;.
Quasarch Console is now waiting for Quasarplane to negotiate and send your container to one of our selected compute providers.
Once the process is complete you&amp;rsquo;ll see the status of the container has changed to &lt;em&gt;deployed&lt;/em&gt;.
If something went wrong the container will have its status as &lt;em&gt;failed&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-warning&#34; role=&#34;alert&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4 class=&#34;alert-heading&#34;&gt;Warning&lt;/h4&gt;

    Currently every container will have its port forwarded to port 80.
Please make sure you set the &lt;code&gt;port&lt;/code&gt; field correctly to point towards the container&amp;rsquo;s exposed port.

&lt;/div&gt;


      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Use Cases</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/use-cases/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page features Container Service&amp;rsquo;s core use cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that the full range of potential use cases is broader than what is covered here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;websites-and-web-applications&#34;&gt;Websites and Web Applications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost every developer will sooner or later need a place to host their website and applications.
Container Service provides an easy deployment experience at a fraction of the price of centralized competitors.
It is perfect for developers that want to host their website without going through the burden of configuring a server and avoiding surprise bills from unwanted usage.
Quasarch will only charge you for the time your run, not the amount of traffic.
Censorship-resistance let&amp;rsquo;s you freely express yourself without fear of being silenced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hpc-workloads&#34;&gt;HPC Workloads&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, businesses and organizations generate and process massive amounts of data in real-time.
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s analyzing user behavior on a website, processing sensor data from IoT devices, or conducting financial market analysis, real-time data processing is critical for making informed decisions promptly.
Big data technologies facilitate the handling of such large volumes of data, and serverless containers enhance the efficiency and scalability of real-time processing tasks.
Container Service&amp;rsquo;s support of GPUs gives engineers the tools to take on HPC tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-delivery-networks&#34;&gt;Content Delivery Networks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized container services can enhance CDNs by deploying containers in various locations across the globe.
This decentralized approach improves content delivery speeds by serving content from servers that are geographically closer to the end-users.
Container Service&amp;rsquo;s price model can help engineers build a global CDN for a fraction of the cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;dapps&#34;&gt;DApps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain-based decentralized applications can utilize container services to manage and run application components.
Each component of the DApp can be encapsulated within a container, providing isolation and security.
Blockchain ensures the integrity and decentralization of the application data and transactions.
Container Service enables web3 developers to deliver on the promise of decentralization by offering a truly decentralized platform to host containerized DApps.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
