<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quasarplane Documentation – Serverless</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/serverless/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Serverless on Quasarplane Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/serverless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Use Cases</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/docs/tutorials/containers/use-cases/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page features Container Service&amp;rsquo;s core use cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that the full range of potential use cases is broader than what is covered here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;websites-and-web-applications&#34;&gt;Websites and Web Applications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost every developer will sooner or later need a place to host their website and applications.
Container Service provides an easy deployment experience at a fraction of the price of centralized competitors.
It is perfect for developers that want to host their website without going through the burden of configuring a server and avoiding surprise bills from unwanted usage.
Quasarch will only charge you for the time your run, not the amount of traffic.
Censorship-resistance let&amp;rsquo;s you freely express yourself without fear of being silenced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hpc-workloads&#34;&gt;HPC Workloads&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world, businesses and organizations generate and process massive amounts of data in real-time.
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s analyzing user behavior on a website, processing sensor data from IoT devices, or conducting financial market analysis, real-time data processing is critical for making informed decisions promptly.
Big data technologies facilitate the handling of such large volumes of data, and serverless containers enhance the efficiency and scalability of real-time processing tasks.
Container Service&amp;rsquo;s support of GPUs gives engineers the tools to take on HPC tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-delivery-networks&#34;&gt;Content Delivery Networks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decentralized container services can enhance CDNs by deploying containers in various locations across the globe.
This decentralized approach improves content delivery speeds by serving content from servers that are geographically closer to the end-users.
Container Service&amp;rsquo;s price model can help engineers build a global CDN for a fraction of the cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;dapps&#34;&gt;DApps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchain-based decentralized applications can utilize container services to manage and run application components.
Each component of the DApp can be encapsulated within a container, providing isolation and security.
Blockchain ensures the integrity and decentralization of the application data and transactions.
Container Service enables web3 developers to deliver on the promise of decentralization by offering a truly decentralized platform to host containerized DApps.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
